Jeremy Broutin





+48 514 865 435 ieremy.broutin@gmail.com in LinkedIn profile





GitHub profile

Skills

Business relationship management: ability to engage with both marketing and development teams. Web programming: ability to read and write JavaScript, HTML and CSS code.

App programming: ability to read ObjC, read and write Swift (iOS app) and Java (Android app) code. Additional skills: frequent usage of Git and GitHub for version controlling, intermediate level on Photoshop, basic usage of Camtasia (video edition tool).

Google products: expert level on Google Analytics, Tag Manager and AdWords.

Projects

(Google) Lead AdWords Mobile App Promotion expansion in EMEA - January 2015 to now

- Identify technical support gap(s) for Mobile App solutions and shortlist Sales priorities account.
- Provide high quality support for technical pitch and implementation (involving ObjC, Swift and/or Java code review) to major app players in the region.
- Participate in several App Day/Think App conferences to promote mobile app promotion solutions and meet with strategic clients.

(Google) Lead Google Tag Manager product adoption in EMEA - January 2014 to June 2014

- Built internal communication, training and support resources for sales teams in collaboration with several stakeholders.
- Provided client-facing support for technical pitch and product implementation (involving JavaScript coding), while educating clients around product abilities and roadmap.

(Tree-Nation) Manage and expand online global community - March 2010 to July 2010

- Lead website community management with 60,000 users and expand social network presence on Facebook and Twitter, reinforce users' interactions with the project/business.
- Participated in website redesign to enhance communautary focus of the project/business (involving sketching on Photoshop).

Relevant Experience

(Google) Solutions Consultant, Wroclaw (Poland) - November 2013 to now

- Provide strategic and technical consultation for Google advertising tracking solutions.
- Lead new products launches and drive adoption, while gathering clients feedback for product improvement and/or existing bugs.
- Partner with different internal stakeholders to enhance efficiency and/or quality of the services delivered to Google's clients.

(Google) Previous experiences:

- Google Analytics Technical Support Associate, Wroclaw (Poland) Mai 2013 to November 2013
- Google AdWords SMB Online Associate, Wroclaw (Poland) July 2011 to Mai 2013

Education

(Post graduation) Udacity iOS Nanodegree - March 2015 to November 2015

• iOS development online degree (programming language: SWIFT)

(Master) Toulouse Business School, Toulouse (France) - September 2008 to Mai 2011

Major: Online business management

(Erasmus) Jÿvaskÿla University of Applied Sciences, Jÿvaskÿla (Finland) - January 2007 to June 2007

• Degree: High tech businesses management

(Bachelor) ISAM Groupe Sup de Co, Amiens (France) - September 2005 to Mai 2008

Major: Marketing